Drew Bradford

Middletown New Jersey, 07748 United States
917.373.3131 drewbradfordxyz@gmail.com www.drewbradford.com

Profile

I'm a JavaScript and QuickBase developer with a tech and insurance background. I create tools to configure and scope services, increase user productivity, reduce business complexity, improve risk management, streamline workflows and provide data insights.

Projects

A UI tool built with JavaScript and QuickBase to define and scope Digital Storage Services. Subject experts configure the content of the page by entering data into the backend which generates a frontend cart-based experience for a second set of users to scope services, enter co-provider information, expenses and custom roles. Both user types do not touch code.

Word Document generation tool for legal agreements spanning the globe. Users have full UI access to edit the language templates. Different variables within the deal change the formatting and language of the documents.

Bid generation script that generates complicated service bundles with a simple form button. The result is a completed bid that is ready for approval. Increasing deal accuracy and user productivity.

Risk category algorithm to assign, measure and flag services that otherwise would have slipped through causing a financial loss.

Skills

QuickBase, Javascript, React, Vue, NodeJS, Figma, Jira, Agile Development, REST API, Relational Database, Pipelines, Formula Fields, Forms, Reports

Employment

Hitachi Vantara - JavaScript QuickBase Developer

June 2020 - May 2024, Remote

CTC Transportation Insurance - QuickBase JavaScript Developer

June 2016 - August 2017, New Jersey

Education

Pratt Institute,

Bachelors Digital Art - Brooklyn, NY 2009-2013